Christopher Gomez

661-281-4853 c.gomez3644@gmail.com

SUMMARY

I am an experienced software engineer working in the video game industry with multiple shipped titles, interactive software, and a background in technology and art. I have a strong work ethic, a desire to exceed expectations, and the ability to adapt to new situations and learn quickly. I am interested in pushing the boundaries between software and human-computer interaction, utilizing the latest cutting edge technologies to create memorable experiences and useful applications.

EXPERIENCE

WayForward Technologies, Full Stack Engineer Backend Systems, Frontend Frameworks, and Unity Engine

Valencia, CA --- 2019 - Current

College of the Canyons, Lead Computer Science Tutor / Technical Support Computer Science tutor, Canvas support, and computer troubleshooter Valencia, CA --- 2017 - 2019

Gamestop Senior Sales Associate

Customer service and retail position and a local video game store. Valencia, CA --- 2015 - 2017

EDUCATION

California State University, Northridge

Aug 2017 - May 2019
Bachelors of Science - Computer Science

College of the Canyons

Aug 2015 - Jun 2017 Associates of Science - Computer Science Associates of Science - Mathematics

SKILLS

- JavaScript/NodeJS/React, C#, Python, C++, CI/CD, Databases,
 Game Engines
- Real Time Networking (Sockets/STT/HLS)
- Systems, Algorithms, Data, Analytics, Retention Strategies, and Monetization
- Exceptional listener and communicator who effectively conveys information verbally and in writing
- Highly analytical thinking with demonstrated talent for identifying, scrutinizing, improving, and streamlining complex work processes.
- Innovative problem-solver who can generate workable solutions and resolve issues quickly and efficiently

REFERENCES

Available upon request.